Guide to the University Archives Web Archive Collection, 2010-ongoing UA.01.15.0014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Student Organizations Series, 2010-ongoing; 6
  - Political and Social Cause Organizations Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 13
    - Dear Old Duke Instagram page, 2015-2018
  - Religious and Cultural Organizations Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 12
    - Arab Students' Organization, 2010-2013
    - Asian Students Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Baha'i Club, 2010
    - Buddhist Community at Duke, 2010-ongoing
    - Bulgarian Association, 2010
    - Cambridge Christian Fellowship, 2010-2012
    - Chinese Students Association, 2010
    - Duke Africa, 2010-2013
    - Duke Campus Crusade for Christ, 2010
    - Duke Catholic Center, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Chapel, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Chapel Choir, 2010-2013
    - Duke Chapel PathWays Student Ministry, 2010-2013
    - Duke Chinese Student and Scholar Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Ethiopian Student Transnational Association (DESTA), 2010-2012
    - Duke Latter-Day Saint Student Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Lutherans, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke MBA Latin American Student Association, 2010-2012
    - Duke Presbyterian Christian Ministry, 2015-ongoing
    - Duke Turkish Students Association, 2010; 2015-ongoing
    - Duke University Fellowship of Christian Athletes, 2010-2014
    - Duke University Hong Kong Student Association, 2010-2015
    - Duke University International Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Korean Students Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Orthodox Christian Student Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Taiwanese Student Association, 2010; 2015
    - Duke Vietnamese Student Association, 2013-2014
    - Hindu Students Association, 2011-2012
    - Impact Christian Fellowship, 2010-ongoing
    - International Students Inc. at Duke, 2010-ongoing
    - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 2011-2012
    - Jazz at the Mary Lou, 2010-2011
    - Joint Youth Organization of Indians at Duke, 2010-2015
    - Manna Christian Fellowship, 2010-ongoing
    - Mi Gente Latin Student Association, 2010-2015
    - Mi Gente Latin Student Association Twitter feed, 2015-ongoing
    - Native American Student Alliance, 2010-2015
    - Muslim Student Association, 2010-ongoing
    - Nomads of North Carolina - (Project of the Muslim Student Association), 2010-2012
    - Persian Students Association, 2010
    - Presbyterian Campus Ministry (formerly Westminster Fellowship at Duke), 2010-ongoing
    - Reformed University Fellowship, 2010-ongoing
    - Rohr Chabbad of UNC Chapel Hill and Duke University, 2010-ongoing
    - Singapore Students Association, 2012-2013
    - South Asian Student's Association, 2010-2012
    - Student Affairs Jewish Life at Duke, 2010-ongoing
    - Students of the Caribbean Association, 2010
    - United in Praise, 2010-2012
    - Wesley Fellowship at Duke, 2010-ongoing
    - Mi Gente, 2020-ongoing
    - Duke Crux, 2020-ongoing
    - Duke Latinx Business Organization, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke SACNAS, 2021-ongoing
  - Service Organizations Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 10
    - Adopt-a-Grandparent, 2010
    - Big Brothers Big Sisters, 2010-2012
    - Black Male Outreach and Education, 2010
    - Camp Kesem, 2010
    - CHANCE Tutoring, 2010-ongoing
    - China Care Club, 2010-2012
    - Circle K International Duke Chapter, 2010-2015
    - Duke College Mentors, 2010-2014
    - Duke Community Garden, 2010
    - Duke Dance Marathon, 2013
    - Duke Dance Marathon Facebook page, 2013-2015
    - Duke Global Medical Brigades, 2010
    - Duke MBA Games, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Partnership for Service, 2010
    - Duke Splash, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Habitat for Humanity Campus Chapter, 2010-2015
    - Duke University Operation Smile Chapter, 2010
    - Duke University Toys and Tales, 2010
    - Duke-Durham Hunger Alliance, 2010
    - Gente Aprendiendo para Nuevas Oportunidades, 2014-ongoing
    - GlobeMed - Duke Chapter, 2014-ongoing
    - Know Your Status, 2010
    - Manna Project International Duke Chapter, 2010
    - Millennium Village Project, 2010-2012
    - Partners for Learning, 2010
    - Partners for Success Project Child, 2010-ongoing
    - REMEDY at Duke, 2012-ongoing
    - Student Veteran's Association, 2010-2012
    - The Doughman, 2010-ongoing
    - The Future is Now, 2010
    - The Public Interest Law Foundation, 2012-ongoing
    - Wilderness Outdoor Opportunities for Durham Students, 2010-2011
    - Wired2Achieve, 2010
    - Womens Institute of Secondary Education & Research, 2010
  - Student Government Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 6
    - Campus Council, 2010-2012
    - Duke Student Government, 2010-2015
    - East Campus Council, 2010-2011
    - Graduate & Professional Student Council', 2010-ongoing
    - Student Organization Finance Committee, 2010-2011
  - The Anti-Resume Project, 2021-ongoing
- Campus Controversies Series, 2014-ongoing; 7
  - A Gay Student Threatened With Death Speaks Out, Civilities Blog Post in the Washington Post, 2015
  - Belle Knox Subseries, 2014; 14
    Websites in this subseries were captured as a document of the student's own response to media exposure. Rumors regarding the student's participation in adult films began to circulate on an online message board and the student gave an anonymous interview to Towerview (The Chronicle). Her real name and personal information circulated online, prompting coverage from external media sources. The subseries includes editorials penned by the student, two interviews conducted with text publications, and three audiovisual interviews.
    - I'm the Duke University Freshman Porn Star and for the First Time I'm Telling the Story in My Own Words, essay in XOJane, 2014
    - I'm Finally Revealing My Name and Face as the Duke Porn Star, essay in XOJane, 2014
    - Q&A The Duke Freshman Porn Star, interview with New York Magazine's The Cut, 2014
    - The Duke Porn Star: Three Waves of Internet Shaming, interview with WUNC public radio, 2014
    - Lauren' Discusses Paying for Duke Tuition Through Porn, WRAL news story, 2014
    - Belle Knox on Piers Morgan, 2014
    - Meet Belle Knox, the Duke Porn Star (As You Might Have Heard), interview with PlayboySFW, 2014
    - Duke Porn Star: I Lost My Financial Aid, editorial on Time Magazine blog, 2014
  - Call To Prayer Subseries, 2015; 15
    The websites in this subseries were captured to document the University's decision and subsequent reversal to give the Duke Muslim community the opportunity to chant the adhan, the Muslim call to prayer, from the Duke Chapel bell tower on Fridays. The subseries includes the associate dean for religious life's editorial announcing the call to prayer, and two articles about Duke's reversal including reactions from the student body.
    - At Duke Chapel, welcoming Muslims with a call to prayer, editorial published in the News & Observer, 2015
    - Duke cancels Muslim call to prayer; cites opposition, safety, article published in the news & Observer, 2015
    - Duke reverses decision to hold Muslim call-to-prayer from Chapel bell tower, article published in the Chronicle, 2015
- Miscellaneous, 2010-ongoing; 8
  - Alumni War Memorial, 2010
  - DukeCheck, 2012-2014
  - Arts and Health at Duke (formerly Health Arts Network), 2010-ongoing
  - Self Knowledge Symposium, 2010
- Publications Series, 2010-ongoing; 5
  - Carpe Noctem Quarterly, 2010-2011
  - Chanticleer, 2010
  - The Chronicle, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Forum for Law & Social Change, 2012-ongoing
  - Duke Law Journal, 2012-ongoing
  - Duke Magazine, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Math Newsletter, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Political Review, 2014-ongoing
  - East Asia Nexus, 2010-2013
  - Encompass, 2013-ongoing
  - Eruditio: Duke University's Undergraduate Humanities Journal, 2010
  - Faith & Leadership: the online magazine of Leadership Education at Duke Divinity School, 2010-ongoing
  - Form, 2010-2015
  - The Gothic Guardian: The Conservative Magazine of Duke University, 2010-2012
  - Hispanic American Historical Review, 2013-ongoing
  - John Spencer Bassett Fund, 2010-2011
  - Latent Image, 2010
  - The Pareto Commons: Reflections on Regulation, Law and Public Policy, 2010-2013
  - Passport Magazine, 2010-2015
  - The Public Domain: Enclosing the Commons of the Mind, 2010-ongoing
  - Religio: An Undergraduate Publication of Christian Thought, 2010-2012
  - Rival Magazine, 2010-ongoing
  - The Standard, 2014-ongoing
  - Synergy: Duke Civic Engagement Magazine, 2010
  - theArchive, 2010
  - Undergraduate Publications Board, 2010-2011
  - Unzipped: the Duke Journal of Gender and Sexuality, 2011-2012
  - Vertices - Undergraduate Research Journal, 2012-2013
  - Juhood Magazine, 2020-ongoing
  - Duke Law Magazine, 2021-ongoing
  - Duke Medical Ethics Journal, 2021-ongoing
- Campus Activism Series, 2015-ongoing
  - #DUBetter collected tweets, 2015-2016; Twitter data harveted using TAGS. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Twitter's terms of service restrict online access to complete Twitter data, and as such, access to the complete tweets must take place in the Rubenstein Library reading room by requesting the appropriate Digital Materials Set. Access to the Tweet IDs is possible via the web by following the link to the Duke Digital Repository below.
    Some materials are electronic records that require special equipment. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - An open letter to President Brodhead, op-ed by Duke Open Campus Coalition in The Chronicle, 2016
  - #DukeEnrage collected tweets, 2015-2016; Twitter data harveted using TAGS. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
  - #DukeYouAreGuilty collected tweets, 2015-2016; Twitter data harveted using TAGS. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
  - Allen Building Sit-In Subseries, 2016
    - Duke Students & Workers in Solidarity, 2016
    - Duke Students & Workers in Solidarity collected tweets, 2016; Twitter data harveted using TAGS and Social Feed Manager. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
    - #DukeOccupation2016 collected tweets, Twitter data harveted using TAGS. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; approximately 1 MB. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
    - #DismantleDukePlantation collected tweets, 2016; Twitter data harveted using TAGS. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; approximately 60 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
    - Duke's Executive Vice President Tallman Trask hit parking attendant with car, accused of using racial slur, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Employees describe hostile, discriminatory environment in Parking and Transportation Services department, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - We demand the removal of 3 top university administrators, op-ed by Duke Students & Workers in Solidarity in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Storify: Students begin sit-in at Allen Building, demand resignation of Executive Vice President Tallman Trask, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Latest coverage of the Allen Building sit-in, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Storify: 'Occupied' banner unveiled outside Allen building as sit-in continues, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Allen Building sit-in students told they will be removed Sunday, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Video: Protestors reiterate demands as Allen Building sit-in continues, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - City Councilwoman Jillian Johnson, Board of Education member Sendolo Diaminah speak to Allen Building sit-in students Sunday morning, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Q&A: 2 students in Allen Building sit-in discuss ongoing talks with administrators, plan moving forward, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Update on Student Protest at Duke; Allen Building to be Closed on Monday, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Allen sit-in students granted amnesty by administrators, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Statement from Duke's executive vice president Tallman Trask, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Saunders: Not the first takeover for this Duke building, column by Barry Saunders in The News & Observer, 2016
    - 'We are staying indefinitely,' article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - 'We're done with demands': Administrators respond to new student demands, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Protesters at Duke stage sit-in, article in The Daily Tarheel, 2016
    - Occupy Duke: students fight for workers' rights, article in The Technician, 2016
    - Through Duke Protests, Sit-ins Student Bodies Momentarily Stop Administrative Machine, essay by graduate student Travis Knoll in the Huffington Post, 2016
    - Message to the Duke Community from President Richard Brodhead, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Allen Building Remains Closed on April 7 with Limited Access for Duke Employees, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Tour guides prepare to navigate protestors during Blue Devil Days, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Allen Building Remains Closed on April 8 with Limited Access for Duke Employees, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Statement from Duke University President Richard Brodhead, post in Duke Today, 2016
    - Allen Building sit-in students exit building after week-long protest, article in The Chronicle, 2016
    - Protesters take down A-Ville tents outside Allen Building, article in The Chronicle, 2016
  - Allen Building Takeover 50th Anniversary collected tweets, 2019; Twitter data harveted using Twarc. Tweet IDs in TXT format; complete tweets in JSON and HTML formats; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA01-15-0014-SET-0001)
  - Duke Workers United reopening demands, 2020
  - DUP Workers Union, 2021-ongoing